-=圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/=-
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 景鲤
翻译: 夏夏潇潇潇 苏菲仙五填坑中 兜兜 水果哥
校对: 影子 veray
我们最初相恋时的梦
# Dreams, dreams of when we had just started things #
# 只属于你我的梦 #
# Dreams of me and you #
很好
Nice.
# 似乎这些回忆 我无法忘怀 #
# It seems, it seems that I can't shake those memories #
# 你是否也有同感 #
# I wonder if you feel the same way too #
# 宝贝 我也是 #
# Girl, I do #
噢 糟糕 是工作上的电话 把音乐调小点声
Oh, shit, it's work. Wait, turn it down. Turn it down.
喂?
Hello?
- 杰西  - 怎么了?
- Jesse.  - What?
我要跟洛杉矶时报的人说点事 你就安静一会儿吧
I have to give a sound bite for the L.A. Times, so no noise for a minute.
我等下可能也有电话 所以如果吵的话 就说明我也在接电话
I might actually get a call too, so if it's noisy, I'll be on a call.
好吧 好了没?
Okay. Ready?
好 今年的潮流趋势是简约舒适风格
All right. This year, all trends will head toward simplicity and comfort.
网络电视播放器...
Things like Roku, Vudu...
菜谱和便装会在市场上大受欢迎
cookbooks and casual wear will see a spike in the market.
我能抽一口吗?
Can I have a drag?
好
Yeah.
- 很完美 谢了  - 你干嘛呢?
- That's perfect. Thanks.  - What'd you do?
说真的 你就不能坐着不动吗?
Seriously, can you not sit still for like two minutes?
我们谈过的 你得戒烟
We talked about this. No more smoking.
- 快看 迪士尼音乐厅  - 我不会这么做
- Hey, Disney Hall.  - Yeah. I'm not doing it.
- 不做什么?  - 我不会进去的
- Not doing what?  - I am not doing that.
- 它只是一栋建筑  - 我懂了 因为那不是潮流
- It's just a building.  - It's not trending.
想玩抓胸游戏吗? 我的手臂比你长 胸还比你小 你输定了
Wanna go titty for titty? My arms are longer. My boobs are smaller.
- 认真开车  - 我很认真...
- Focus on driving.  - I am focused on dri...
- 很好  - 杰西 那地方真神奇
- Great.  - Jess, that place is amazing.
我在接重要电话
I'm on a really important call.
- 噢 好的  - 我都不知道该说什么了
- Oh, okay.  - Yeah. I don't know what to say.
- 谢谢您的电话  - 是关于那工作的?
- Thank you for calling.  - Is that about the job?
好极了 非常感谢
Awesome. Thank you so much, man.
谢谢 好 尽快联系 好 再见
Thank you, yeah. Talk soon. Okay, bye.
- 是那份杂志社的工作吗?  - 不是
- Was that about the magazine job?  - No.
不过 塞莱斯特 昨晚有个大潮来了
But, Celeste, a swell came in last night.
就在西北面
Northwest.
很明显 这浪又大又清
Apparently, it is overhead and it is glassy.
- 你到底在说什么?  - 马里布
- What the fuck are you talking about?  - Malibu.
- 那里波浪正涌  - 你在说冲浪? 你竟然在说冲浪
- The waves are crushing right now.  - Are you talking about surfing? You're talking about surfing.
对啊 你为什么不兴奋了?
Yeah. Why are you not more excited?
我好激动 刚才我以为是杂志社打来的
I'm so psyched. I just thought that was about that job.
- 那个插画工作  - 对 他们没回我电话
- The illustration job.  - Right. They haven't called me back.
说实话 我不是很想在那儿工作
Honestly, I'm not dying to work there.
听上去你根本就不想工作
Doesn't seem like you're dying to work at all.
我在准备一个展览 你知道要卖出去东西很花时间
I'm putting together a show. I'm going to sell stuff. You know it takes time.
- 我了解  - 那好 现在我可以载你回家了吗?
- I know. I know.  - Okay. Can I drop you off at home now?
- 我刚错过了一道波浪  - 我觉得吧...
- I just missed a wave.  - At some point, I feel...
- 又一道  - 好吧
- Missed another.  - All right.
- 又错过两个  - 好的
- Two more just went by.  - Okay.
- 我本可以激情冲浪的  - 送我回家吧
- I could be on those.  - Take me home.
- 六点钟回来好吗? 这样就还能洗个澡  - 为什么要洗澡?
- Be back by 6 so you can shower?  - Why shower?
- 约了贝丝和塔克一起吃晚饭  - 那好吧
- Beth and Tucker, dinner.  - Right. Yep.
- 祝你冲浪愉快  - 噢 想着就爽
- Have fun shredding your glassy peel.  - Oh, so wrong.
- 爱你  - 爱你
- Love you.  - Love you.
谢了
Thank you.
结果你们上周去看那个乐队表演了?
Did you guys end up seeing that band last week?
没错 是说草泥马乐队吧?
Oh, yeah. Fuck Your Mom?
- 他们很棒 老兄  - 对
- They were for reals, dude.  - Yeah.
可以请他们当你的婚礼乐队 他们很吵不过却很便宜
You should get them as your wedding band. They're loud but probably pretty cheap.
或者帮他们开场的神佑世人乐队也不错
Or the band that opened for them, Please us, Christ. They were good.
- 他们棒极了  - 我告诉过你们 这事儿已经定下来了
- They kind of shredded.  - Guys, It's done. I told you.
我们请到了最好的摇摆乐队
We've already got the greatest swing band in New England.
- 糖足和摇摆鱼乐队  - 没有 其实没请
- Sugarfoot and the Swingin' Scrod.  - No, no, no. We actually didn't.
我们商量过 摇摆音乐太过时了
We talked about this. Swing is so late 90s.
我们不请摇摆乐队 我们...
We're not gonna do that. We're not doing it. We're not...
我要亲遍你的脸 爱死你了
I'm gonna eat your face, I love you so much.
- 我们等下再说  - 那现在我们看看菜单
- We'll talk about it later.  - And so now we turn to the menu.
好 我觉得最好点玉米饼和玉米卷...
Yes, I think the best idea is to get enchiladas and tacos...
然后分着吃?
and then we split the two, ja?
这是一个不错的选择 但我还是要反对...
This is a clinical choice, but I must object to your strategy...
因为我想独自享受玉米卷
for I wish to enjoy the tacos alone.
不 这不公平 我就咬一口 不行吗?
No, but that is not fair. As long as I can have some bites, ja?
- 但我们都知道你的"咬一口"是什么意思  - 才没有
- But we know about your bites, don't we?  - No.
你咬完一口 就会接着咬很多口
You take one and then you take many.
- 这是真的  - 哦 就是
- Ja, this is true.  - Ja, you do.
这是真的
This is true.
我们不能再这样下去了
We can't do this anymore.
天啊
Oh, God.
亲爱的 婚礼会有压力 但是我向你保证
Honey, weddings are so stressful, but I promise you, we know.
- 你们会很好的  - 很好的
- You guys will be fine.  - Just fine.
- 对 我们很好  - 对 我们很好
- Yeah. Oh, yeah, we are fine.  - No, we're good.
你们到底在干嘛?
What the fuck are you two doing?
- 什么意思?  - 对 你什么意思?
- What do you mean?  - Yeah. What do you mean?
我什么意思? 你们两个不在一起了
What do I mean? You two are not together.
很不正常 好吗?
It's not normal, okay?
你们已经分开六个月了
You guys have been separated for six months.
都要离婚了 知道不?
You're getting divorced, all right?
可是你们两个还每天同进同出 好像根本没离婚这回事
And you spend every day together hanging out as if, like, it's no big deal.
- 知道吗 这非常奇怪  - 少说两句吧...
- Guess what. It's fucking weird.  - I don't think this is...
- 告诉他们你的感觉  - 我们都别装了 真的好奇怪的
- No. Tell them what you think.  - Let's not play charades. It's weird.
- 我们根本没在装呀  - 没有
- There's no charades being played here.  - No charades.
- 根本没有  - 就是
- No charading.  - No.
我们离婚了 但还是朋友 你们应该高兴才对
We are separated, and we're friends. You guys should be happy.
以前我们老是吵架 现在都不吵了
We fought all the time. We don't anymore.
你们应该兴奋才对 都不用选边站 这才是完美离婚
You should be thrilled. You don't have to choose sides. It's the perfect breakup.
对 对大家都好
Yeah, everyone's cool.
- 大家都不好  - 不好
- Everyone is not cool.  - Not cool.
这里没人好
No one is cool here.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我实在受不了了 抱歉
I can't do this anymore. I'm sorry.
- 宝贝  - 贝丝
- Baby.  - Beth.
- 贝丝很生气  - 嗯 她气疯了
- Beth is so angry.  - Ja, she is buber angry.
这太奇怪了
This is too weird.
嘿 小赛
Hey, C.
- 你能帮我个忙吗?  - 什么?
- Can you help me with something?  - What?
我不想给你压力...
Don't wanna pressure you into anything...
但这位先生实在是寂寞难耐...
but this gentleman is awfully lonely and just...
把手伸过来 我告诉你怎么做 只要...
Here, I'll show you how it works. Just...
- 摸到了  - 噢 爽死了
- Oh, my God.  - Oh, God.
- 噢  - 噢
- Oh, God.  - Oh, God.
哦 就是这样
Oh, he likes that.
小点声
Wait, be quiet.
我室友就在隔壁 别出声
My roommate's next door. Don't make any sound.
- 就是这样 好爽  - 天啊
- All right. Oh, God.  - Oh, God.
哦 对 用力 好爽
Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God.
- 伙计  - 出来得真多
- Dude.  - That was a big one.
嗯
Yeah.
- 贝丝和塔克生气了  - 对
- Beth and Tucker are crazy.  - Crazy.
- 对吧?  - 没错
- Right?  - Yes.
我是说我们同进同出并不奇怪
I mean, it is not weird that we hang out all the time.
你觉得我们同进同出奇怪吗?
Do you think it's weird we hang out all the time?
- 不 你是我的好朋友  - 对 你也是我的好朋友
- No. You're my best friend.  - Yeah. You're my best friend too.
上次我们冷战超过一星期是在十年级...
Last time we didn't speak for more than a week was in 10th grade...
就是你去加拿大太空营的时候
when you went to Space Camp Canada.
那五个星期好痛苦
That was a brutal five weeks.
那失重体验真的很棒
The antigravity training was crazy, though.
不过我很想你
But I missed you.
我也是
Me too.
看看谁回来了
Look who's back.
- 他恢复得很快  - 哦 不
- His recovery time is insane.  - Oh, no.
他是个大学生 准备好再来一发了
He's a college boy and he's ready to rock.
就是这样
Here we go.
- 我累死了  - 我也是
- I'm exhausted.  - Yeah, me too.
- 甜品很棒 对吧?  - 是很不错
- Dessert was good, right?  - Oh, so good.
- 晚安  - 晚安
- Night.  - Night.
嘿 今天晚上挺冷的 你那边的制热怎么样?
Hey, it's kind of chilly tonight. How's your heat in there?
- 很好 没事  - 好 那就好
- It's fine. I'm fine.  - Okay. Good.
嘿 很抱歉我还住在这里
Hey, sorry I'm still living back here.
你想住多久就多久 这是你的工作室
Stay as long as you want. It's your studio.
- 而且有你在这里真好  - 我也觉得
- Also, it's really nice having you here.  - For me too.
- 晚安  - 晚安 爱你
- Night.  - Night. Love you.
我也爱你
Love you too.
- 你是要...?  - 您点的印度拉茶
- Are you gonna...? No.  - Here's your chai latte.
- 能给我杯大杯咖啡吗?  - 大卫先生点了杯大豆卡布奇诺
- Can I get a large coffee to go?  - Soy cappuccino for David.
抱歉 先生
Excuse me, sir? Sir.
先生 对 就是你
Sir. Yeah, you. Sorry.
你知道插了很多人的队吗?
You do realize that you just cut in front of a bunch of people, right?
- 我很抱歉 我不知道  - 你不知道?
- I'm so sorry. I didn't know.  - Did you not know?
- 我很急 所以...  - 所以你是知道的
- I'm just in a big rush, so...  - So you did know.
- 我确定这里排队的人都很急  - 好吧 你真的要跟我争论吗?
- And I'm sure everyone here is in a rush.  - Okay, is this really happening?
她在看糕点 所以我想...
She was looking at the pastries, so I just... I thought...
不只是她 是她后面的所有人
It's not just her. It's everyone behind her.
如果你想问一下是不是所有人都不介意 请便
If you wanna ask every single person if it's okay that you cut, be my guest.
别以为自己的时间比别人的重要
Don't assume your time is more important than others'.
谢谢你的演讲 祝大家今天愉快 除了你
Thank you for the lecture. Have a great day, everybody. Not you.
美国文化正在死去 这个国家正在萌生一种无情的喜好...
American culture is dying, and there's an unrelenting appetite in this country...
例如真人秀 像赖利・班克斯这样毫无天赋的流行明星...
for reality shows, talentless pop stars like Riley Banks...
以及陈词滥调的系列电影
recycled, bloated movie franchises.
我们越是消费这些废物 就会越想接着消费
The more we consume crap, the more we want crap.
人如其食
You are what you eat.
听起来毫无希望了 这就是结果吗?
It sounds utterly hopeless. Is there an upshot?
我想会有一个大潮流 趋向简约朴素
I think there will be a groundswell movement toward simplicity.
人们会渴望精神 心理和身体的营养
People will crave spiritual, mental and physical nourishment.
- 会追求最基础的东西  - 这很值得品味
- It'll be back to basics.  - A lot to chew on.
想要继续探究这个沉重却有趣的话题...
For more on this gloomy but interesting subject...
欢迎购买塞莱斯特・马汀的新书...
look out for Celeste Martin's new book, Shitegeist...
星期一上市
on bookshelves Monday.
- 昨晚我和闹剧二人组吃饭了  - 谁?
- I had dinner with the drama club last night.  - Who's that?
贝丝和塔克 他们吃到一半就走了...
Beth and Tucker. They left in the middle of dinner...
因为他们不支持我和杰西在一起 你能想象吗?
because they don't approve of me and Jesse hanging out. Can you believe that?
我们很好 如果我们是同性恋 就不会有这段对话
It is so judgy. We're fine. If we were gay, we wouldn't be having this conversation.
- 我们只是朋友 根本没想这么多  - 你们还没准备让对方离开
- We'd just be friends. We don't even think about it.  - You are not ready to let go of each other.
- 这完全没错呀  - 的确没错
- There's nothing wrong with that.  - There's nothing wrong with it.
- 我在问你的想法  - 老实说吧...
- I mean, what do you think?  - Well, to be honest...
天啊 我们要签下赖利・班克斯?
Oh, my God. We're signing Riley Banks?
怎么回事 斯科特? 我刚才还在电视上说她是垃圾
What the fuck, Scott? I just trashed her on TV.
这就是我把你叫到办公室的原因 这是件大事
That's why I wanted you to come in. It's a huge account.
我们组建公司 就是为了不要去签像赖利・班克斯这样的人
We built this company so we didn't have to sign accounts like Riley Banks.
如果不签赖利・班克斯 这公司就可能会倒闭
You and I may not have a company if we don't take Riley Banks.
我不明白 她就只有绯闻和难看发型而已
I don't understand. She's like a vagina and a hairdo.
她要发行一张新专辑了
She's releasing a new CD.
她想要我们公司发行和推广
She wants us to do the branding and merchandising.
好吧 我去把意见往肚子里吞
Fine. I'm gonna go eat my feelings.
如果你想要我的意见 我的确认为你该去约约会
If you want my opinion, I do think you should start dating.
斯科特 我没事 我时间很多 所以不担心
Scott, I'm fine. I have so much time. I'm not worried.
帮我一个忙 你换对象之前 可千万别乱搞
Do me a favor and get your fuck on before you meet the next guy.
这算什么? 你在做什么?
What is that? What are you doing?
抱歉 我想假装是你可爱的同志朋友
Sorry. I was trying to be your saucy gay friend.
- 感觉不太好  - 不 别这样
- Didn't feel good.  - No. Don't.
经济状况真是不好 老兄
The economic climate is real bad, man.
我觉得自己的生意从没这么艰难过
I think my business is taking the hardest hit of all.
这很残酷 是只有我生意凄惨还是都没人开口?
It's brutal. Is it just me or is nobody talking about it?
- 你可是买烟草的 斯基尔斯  - 现在不是了
- You sell weed, Skillz.  - Not for long, dude.
你看到满地都是烟草店了吗?
You seen those weed pharmacies on every fucking corner?
他们要把我杀死了
They're killing me.
我是说 我在想改行 卖点冰毒
I mean, I think I gotta branch out, start working in methamphetamines.
或者去教幼儿园 知道不?
Or teach preschool, you know?
我喜欢孩子 而且我一直都想去教幼儿园
I love kids, and I just, I don't know, always wanted to do that.
抱歉 兄弟
Sorry, dude.
我知道这是很严肃的话题 但看看那姑娘的屁屁
I know this is serious talky time, but look at the fucking seat on that girl.
- 还真是翘啊  - 还没结束
- That is a party.  - I don't think it's over.
- 什么? 她的屁股? 不 它永远都在  - 不 兄弟 是说我和塞莱斯特
- What? Her butt? No, it goes on forever.  - No, man. Me and Celeste.
她有压力还很困惑 但是我想她开始接受了
She's overwhelmed and confused, but I think she's gonna come around.
不是吧 兄弟?
Oh, no. Really, pal?
我是说已经有段时间了...
I mean, it's been a while, you know...
但是时候看清现实 继续生活了
but I think it's time to accept that and move on.
- 对吧? 给维罗妮卡打电话  - 不 哥们 这不是一夜情
- Right? Call that dime Veronica.  - No, dude. That was a one-time thing.
塞莱斯特还不知道这件事 别告诉她
Celeste does not know about it, so don't tell her.
我不知道还要敌进我退 好像你没那么喜欢她...
I didn't know that was a hit-and-run. It's not like you really liked her, so...
她很好 不过她不是塞莱斯特
She was cool, but she's not Celeste.
但你要记住 不能脚踏两条船
Okay, but remember, you can't reheat a souffle.
- 什么意思?  - 这里是洛杉矶 到处是美女
- What does that mean?  - It's L.A. There's bettys everywhere.
的确得提醒一下塞莱斯特 你还是很有吸引力的 对吧?
It's good to remind Celeste you can pull a little wool, right?
- 让她紧张一下  - 对
- Make her sweat a bit.  - Yeah, I guess.
- 你还好吗?  - 非常好
- How are you?  - Good.
- 那你想怎么样?  - 我不想重新开始
- So, what do you want, man?  - Maybe I just don't wanna start over.
不 我是问你想要吃什么? 酸奶怎么样?
No, I meant, like, what do you want? Do you want yogurt?
我要枸杞绿茶加酸奶薯条和麦片
Can I have a goji-berry-and-green-tea swirl with yogurt chips and Cap'n Crunch?
- 你想和我朋友出去玩吗?  - 别这样
- Would you go out with my friend ever?  - No.
你老婆在哪? 你们两个每天都一起来这里
Where's your wife? You guys are here every day together.
- 我和老婆离婚了  - 哦 好的
- We're actually separated.  - Oh, cool.
我是说 不管怎么样 我答应了
I mean, bummer or whatever, but, okay, I'll go.
就是这样
Just like that.
好极了
Cool.
你想把料搅进去还是放在一边?
You want it swirled or side by side?
- 怎么了?  - 我要说一件事
- What?  - I need to say one thing.
以后我就不会再说了
Then I'm not gonna say another word about it.
我很抱歉那天在晚餐时发火 可是我认为你们不在一起是很愚蠢的
I'm sorry I wigged on you at dinner. But I think it's stupid you're not together.
我知道 你们是好朋友
I do. You guys are best friends.
这就是重点 其它事情都没关系
That's the hard part. Nothing else matters.
贝丝 我深爱着杰西...
Beth, I love Jesse dearly...
但是他既没存款 也没像样的衣服
but he doesn't have a checking account or dress shoes.
我孩子的父亲要有车 知道吗?
The father of my children will have a car. You know?
杰西会一直是我的好朋友
Jesse will always be my best friend.
好吧 我说了我该说的
Okay. I said what I had to say.
以后不会再说了 我只是必须要说出来
Not gonna say another word. I just needed to say that.
他住在客房就是个大错误
It's a huge mistake that he's living in that guesthouse.
- 塞莱斯特 你这是在煎熬他的心  - 杰西没事
- Celeste, you are breaking his heart, slowly.  - Jesse is fine.
他很好
He's fine.
嘿
Hey.
你不工作?
You're not working?
又在看北京奥运会?
You're watching the Beijing Olympics again?
而且又哭了
And you're crying again.
马赛厄斯的老婆去年出车祸死了
Matthias' wife died in a car accident last year.
嘿 你完成流行论坛的艺术画了吗?
Hey, did you finish that artwork for the Pop Formm website yet?
没 还没完成 我还在画
No, it's not done yet. I'm still working on it.
- 我想你会喜欢的  - 今晚能完成吗?
- I think you're gonna like it.  - Can you finish it tonight?
不 实际上...
No. Actually...
坐下来 我要告诉你一些重要的事
sit down for one second. I wanna tell you something important.
好
Okay.
如果是你欠我工作的事...
Does it have something to do with the work you owe me...
现在才谈是不是有点晚了?
that's late that we were just talking about?
今晚我要去约会
Tonight I am going on a date.
和别人约会
And I'm gonna date people.
很好啊
That's great.
- 是吗?  - 嗯
- It is?  - Yeah.
杰西 别哭了 真为你高兴
No, Jess. Please don't cry again. Good for you.
- 你不困扰吗?  - 不
- Doesn't bother you?  - No.
好吧 是个酸奶店的服务员
Okay. Yeah, it's yogurt girl from Yogurt Yurt.
那个酸奶妹很可爱
Yogurt girl. Yeah, she's cute.
- 她很年轻 对吧?  - 非常年轻
- She's really young, right?  - Super young, yeah.
- 但她的身材就一般了  - 好吧 没必要这样 但是...
- But her body is, like, all-time.  - Okay, there's no need for that, but...
哇 那很好啊 真的很好
Wow, that's great. That's really great.
那就好 找下个老婆前就该约约会
This is good. You gotta crawl before you walk.
虽然她不会是你下一任老婆 但无所谓了
She's not gonna be wife number two, but whatever.
不 这只是个约会
No. It's just a date.
嘿 大进展
Hey. Big move.
我为你自豪
I'm proud of you.
- 谢了  - 我能起来了吗?
- Thank you.  - Can I get up now?
- 可以  - 好
- Oh, yeah.  - Okay.
约会顺利 以后再联系
You're gonna be great. Call me after.
不
No.
我当年还在念书 但我辍学了 因为我太想在时尚圈工作了
I was in school, but I dropped out because I really wanna work in fashion.
但真的很难找一个带薪实习的工作
But it's really hard to find a paid internship.
所以我回到学校 然后现在在酸奶店工作
So I went back to school, and now I work at Yogurt Yurt.
赚钱做我喜欢的事
I'm looking to make money doing something I love.
我确定世界都会支持我
I'm sure the universe has my back.
好的事情总会来的 知道吗?
The right thing will come along, you know?
- 很明显你明白了 对吗?  - 完全明白
- I mean, you get it, obviously, right?  - Totally.
天啊
Oh, my God.
天啊 杰西
Oh, my God, Jesse.
"在我脸上做"?
"Do It on My Face"?
这首歌是关于怎么做自己的
This song is about being who you are.
除非你很逊
Unless who you are sucks.
所有人闭嘴
Everybody shut up.
他们说会在最新上架的地方
They said it would be in new releases.
在哪呢?
Where is it?
没有
No.
这就是我说的陈列问题
Now, that's what I call placement.
即使是你的书 你也不能偷
You shouldn't steal it, even if it is your book.
我只是要重新换个位置
I'm just rearranging some things.
- 好了  - 你不能这样做
- There.  - You can't do that.
- 我可以  - 书店的人没有选你的书
- Yes, I can.  - An employee didn't pick you.
没关系
Doesn't matter.
嘿 书店选了你的书
Hey. Employee picks.
- 恭喜了 酷毙了  - 谢了
- Congrats. That's awesome.  - Thanks.
- 怎么了?  - 书店选了她的书
- What happened?  - Employee picks.
杰西?
Jesse?
- 嘿  - 维罗妮卡
- Hey.  - Veronica.
- 嘿  - 嘿
- Hey.  - Hey.
- 最近怎样?  - 很好
- How's it going?  - Good.
- 是吗?  - 嗯
- Yeah?  - Yeah.
- 你最近怎样?  - 我很好啊
- How you been?  - I've been good.
- 你呢?  - 我也是
- How have you been?  - Good.
- 你看起来不错  - 谢了 你也是
- You look great.  - Thanks. You too.
你在这干嘛?
What are you doing here?
找几本书
Checking out books.
- 我也是  - 嗯
- Same.  - Yep.
你的晾衣夹插画画得怎么样了?
How's your clothespin collage going?
你还记得那个
You remember that.
很好 虽然速度慢 但很顺利
It's good. It's good. Slow but good.
呃 别放弃 因为那很特别 也很漂亮
Well, don't give it up, because it's really unique and beautiful.
- 我希望听起来没那么...  - 不 不 很谢谢你这么说...
- I hope that didn't sound too...  - No, no. That's really sweet and...
- 好吧  - 对我意义颇深 谢了
- Good.  - Yeah, that means a lot. Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
那晚我和你玩得很开心 很抱歉没有打电话给你
I had so much fun with you that night. I'm sorry I didn't call.
我也很开心
I had a lot of fun too.
棒极了
Cool.
- 嘿  - 嗨
- Hey.  - Hi.
我得多找些地方放我的书
I have to find more places to put my book.
维罗妮卡 这些是我朋友
Veronica, these are my friends.
- 这是塞莱斯特  - 你好
- Celeste.  - Hi.
- 贝丝 还有塔克  - 你好
- Beth and Tucker.  - Hi.
- 你好  - 嗨
- Hey.  - Hi.
- 你好 很高兴认识你  - 我也是
- How are you? Nice to meet you.  - Nice to meet you too.
这本书是你写的
You wrote that book.
我在网上看了它的摘要 很吸引人
I just read an excerpt online. It's really compelling.
- 谢谢 谢谢你这么说  - 不客气
- Thank you. Thank you so much. That's very nice.  - You're welcome.
很高兴认识你们
Well, nice to meet you.
- 拜  - 拜
- Bye.  - Bye.
- 再见  - 再见
- Bye.  - See you later.
拜
Bye.
- 再见  - 她是谁?
- Bye.  - What was that?
维罗妮卡
Veronica.
- 什么情况?  - 没什么
- Story?  - No story.
只是我前段时间认识的女孩儿罢了
Just a girl I met a little while ago.
她挺漂亮的 像年轻时的我
She's pretty. She looks like a young me.
打扰一下 嗨
Excuse me. Hi.
我想送几本Shitegeist给朋友...
Do you have any more copies of this book Shitegeist...
你们还有多的吗? 听说这书相当不错呢
for me to give to my friends? Because I heard it's excellent.
- 别接 别接  - 稍等一会儿 喂
- No, no.  - Just one second. Hey.
- 刚看完表演  - 怎么样?
- Just got out of the show.  - How was it?
- 简直酷毙了  - 你现在忙吗?
- Fucking dope.  - Hey, are you busy now?
- 不 我不忙  - 能过来帮我装一下梳妆台吗?
- No, I'm not busy.  - Can you help me build this dresser?
- 好  - 我一个人装不了
- Okay.  - I can't do it alone.
- 好吧 我马上过去 拜  - 杰西 我需要你
- All right, all right. Okay, bye.  - Jesse, I need you.
伙计 我得回家了
Dude, I gotta go home.
表演完了有余兴派对
After the show, it's the after-party.
我知道 但是她买了个宜家的梳妆台 需要我帮她"装一下"
I know, but she's got an IKEA dresser she needs me to help her "build."
哦 真是这样?
Oh, it's like that?
我跟你说过 她只是需要更多的时间来适应
I told you, man, she just needed a little bit more time.
- 我明白的  - 喔 她很快就会懂了
- I got this.  - Oh, she's about to get it.
我在这儿 该死的瑞典人(宜家是瑞典公司)
I'm in here. Fuck Sweden.
怎样了?
What up?
- 造布鲁克林大桥也比这个容易  - 没问题 就是个梳妆台而已
- It's easier to build the Brooklyn Bridge.  - We got this. It's just a dresser.
真该死 我靠!
Fucking fuck. Fuck me!
难道他们故意造了一件组装不好的家具...
What, do they make a piece of furniture that's impossible to build on purpose...
专门跟你作对?
just to fuck with you?
谢谢夸奖
Thank you.
等等
Wait.
我知道了
I've got it.
- 太完美了  - 完美的接合
- Perfect.  - Fucking layup.
就像孔思风格加上巴斯奎特涂鸦风...
It's like Koons meets Basquiat meets...
再加上塞拉...
Serra meets...
和"春风吹又生"里的科尔奇风
Corky from Life Goes On.
- 他是素食者  - 哦 珍惜吧
- He's a vegan, you know.  - Oh, cherish.
- 太可爱了  - 你才可爱
- That is so cute.  - You're cute.
你才可爱
You're cute.
你在干什么?
Hey. What are you doing?
我爱你
I love you.
好了
Okay.
真是个馊主意 对不起
That was a bad idea. So sorry.
不 别抱歉 这很好
No, don't be sorry. It was nice.
杰西
Jess.
行了
Come on.
我们喝醉了 那个梳妆台...
Drinking and the dresser and....
我想 你懂的... 我们都在跟别人约会
I think, you know.... We're seeing other people.
是 但那都是因为...
Well, yeah, but just because....
天啊
Oh, God.
我真是个白痴
I'm an idiot.
- 我只是觉得...  - 你觉得什么?
- I just thought...  - You thought what?
我那时候头脑不清了 否则不会让这一切发生的
Well, I wasn't clearly thinking, or else I wouldn't have let that happen.
你不会觉得我们又在一起了吧
You didn't think we were getting back together.
这不像...
It's not like....
你大可以打电话给宜家的人
You know, there's a guy you can call at IKEA.
他会帮你装好梳妆台 你该打给他
He'll build your dresser for you. You should call him.
没准也会跟你上床
Probably fuck you too.
- 哦 杰西  - 我真他妈是个白痴
- Oh, Jess.  - I'm a fucking idiot.
哦 杰西 别这样
Oh, Jess, come on. Jesse.
杰西?
Jess?
嘿 杰西 是我
Hey, Jess, it's me.
我正在去机场的路上 但我想跟你谈谈
I'm on my way to the airport, but I wanted to talk to you.
我不知道昨晚发生了什么
I don't know what happened last night.
希望你没事
I hope you're okay.
就这样 拜 打给我
Okay, bye. Call me.
嗨 我是杰西 请留言
Hey, you've reached Jesse. Leave me a message.
嘿 还是我
Hey, it's me again.
我在旧金山 明天要去波士顿
I'm in San Francisco. I'm going to Boston tomorrow.
还有 我想你
And I miss you.
打给我 就这样 拜
Call me. Okay. Bye.
对不起
I'm sorry.
当然
Of course.
真是傻瓜
Stupid.
嘿 你回来了 我想跟你谈谈
Hey, you're back. I wanna talk to you.
我知道 我也想跟你谈谈
I know. I wanna talk to you too.
你去哪儿了? 两星期都不见人影
Where have you been? It's been like two weeks.
有好多好玩的事
There's so much to lay down.
你知道吗 按次计费的黄色视频有广东话的了
Like, did you know, the pay-per-view porn is available in Cantonese now.
- 真的?  - 是啊
- Really?  - Yeah.
我在你家附近 我可以过来吗? 这件事挺重要的
I'm really near your house. Can I just come by? It's kind of important.
波士顿有68所大学 为什么我公司里的大学生们却这么蠢?
There's 68 colleges in Boston. Why were the kids in my group so dumb?
我是说 跟他们就根本讲不通话
I mean, they were, like, barely making sense.
- 他们说的不是英语 他们...  - 嘿 我要告诉你一些事
- They were not speaking English. They were...  - Hey. I really gotta tell you something.
实际上 我也是
Actually, me too.
等等 你是同性恋?
Wait. Are you gay?
快承认吧 那不知道多有趣
Please tell me you're gay. That'd be so funny.
不是同性恋 这一定很难相信...
No. Not gay. This is going to be hard to believe...
- 你又换了个女朋友  - 我有孩子了
- But you went on another date.  - I'm having a baby.
- 我有孩子了  - 什么意思?
- I'm having a baby.  - What do you mean?
我要当爸爸了
I'm having a child.
跟别的女人?
With another person?
是的 跟别的女人
Yes, with another person.
等等 什么?
Wait, what?
对不起 这...?
Sorry. What...?
这到底怎么回事? 跟谁?
What the fuck? With who?
其实你见过她 那天在书店里
You met her, actually, the other day at the bookstore.
但这在生理上不可能啊 才两个星期
But that's not even physically possible. That was two weeks ago.
是的
Yeah.
事实上 我三个月前跟她上的床
Truth is, I slept with her like three months ago.
该死 好吧
Shit. Okay.
我都不知道这些 但现在已经不重要了 好吧
Well, I didn't know about that, but that's not important right now. Okay.
你需要我做什么?
What do you need me to do?
不 你不需要做任何事
Oh, no. You don't have to do anything.
我真的想跟她好好走下去
I really wanna make it work with her.
我去下洗手间
Excuse me one second.
你好
Hello.
- 什么?  - 我说 你好
- What?  - I said, hello.
你好
Hi.
- 你练得如何?  - 我练得如何?
- How's your practice?  - How's my practice?
- 很好  - 我帮你放垫子
- It's fine.  - I'll get that mat for you.
- 谢谢  - 我常在这儿看见你
- Thanks.  - I see you here a lot.
你的战士二式做得很好
You've got a great Warrior 2.
你的四点支撑式平衡得让人难以置信
Your Chaturanga is, like, incredibly balanced.
我还在继续学习那个姿势... 你是单身吗?
I'm still working that position, but... are you single?
你真的要跟我搭讪吗? 你现在确实在跟我搭讪
Are you really doing this right now? You're really doing this right now.
我知道 我得争取啊 我平时不这样的 它就这么发生了 我要...
I know. I'm gonna go for it. I don't do this. It's just happening. I'm gonna....
- 要迅速采取行动  - 我已经在行动了
- Gonna jump right in there.  - I'm jumping in.
搭讪队长
Captain Conversation.
你是...? 嘿 我叫保罗 放这儿吧
Do you...? Hey, I'm Paul. Put it there.
- 我叫塞莱斯特  - 塞莱斯特啊
- Celeste.  - Celeste.
这名字不错 这是我的名片
That's a great name. So here's my card.
那是我的电话 邮箱 如果你要发传真...
That's my number, e-mail. If you need to fax me...
你带着名片来上瑜伽课?
You bring cards to yoga?
嗨 还好吗? 过来吧
Hi. How are you? Come on in.
今天的沉浸体验练得不错
Great flow today.
- 我不擅长追别人 给点意见?  - 金融分析师 不错嘛
- I'm not good at this. Little help?  - Financial analyst. Cool.
还行 没那么好 过得去吧
Not really. It's not that cool. It's all right.
- 你有告诉我你是干什么的吗?  - 没有
- Did you tell me what you did for a living?  - No, I didn't.
你会告诉我吗? 我很想知道
Well, will you? I'd love to know.
我是时尚趋势预测师 我预测潮流
I'm a trend forecaster. I forecast trends.
时尚趋势预测师 真酷
Trend forecaster. Yeah.
你说真的? 对不起 我以为你在耍我
You serious? I'm sorry I thought you were just fucking with me.
你把你的保时捷换成了奥迪 是因为你怕丢了工作
You traded in your Porsche for an Audi because you're afraid you'll lose your job.
你买安卓手机是因为这让你看起来更加商务...
You just bought a Droid because it makes you seem business-oriented...
而不像苹果 更适合少女们
unlike the iPhone, which you think is for teenage girls.
你练瑜伽是因为你念的是次于常春藤联盟的大学
You go to yoga because you went to a sub-lvy League school.
过去10年不得不长时间工作 周末买醉
You spent the last 10 years working long hours, drinking on weekend
现在你觉得是时候慰藉下心灵了
You thought it was time to do something spiritual.
很高兴认识你 保罗
It was nice to meet you, Paul.
- 嘿  - 嘿
- Hey.  - Hey.
- 早上纽约那边打电话来的时候你去哪儿了?  - 我想你能应付
- Where were you on the New York call this morning?  - I figured you could handle it.
好吧 随你怎么说 艺术品从柏林送来了
Yeah. Well, anyway, the artwork came in from Berlin.
- 东西不错 但是...  - 重磅消息
- It's good, but it...  - Breaking news.
杰西要和别的女人生孩子了
Jesse is having a baby with some girl.
你不知道他在跟别人约会吗?
Did you even know he was seeing someone?
不是 是他几个月前睡过的女人
No, it's somebody he slept with once months ago.
现在他要跟她"走下去" 这消息比空难还爆炸
Now he's gonna try to "make it work." Plane crash.
我不知道该说什么
I don't even know what to say.
我很抱歉 塞莱斯特 你还好吧?
I'm so sorry, Celeste. Are you okay?
斯科特 我非常好 真的
Scott, I'm totally fine. Yes.
- 真的?  - 是啊
- Are you?  - Yes.
我本来就没打算为他生孩子 现在这样对他也好
I wasn't gonna have his baby, so good for him.
我现在不爱他了 所以就更容易就接受事实啦
I'm not in love with him anymore. It makes it easier, you know.
- 事实上我晚上还有约会呢  - 那就好
- I have a date tonight, actually.  - That's great.
出去约个会 被别人仰慕也是件不错的事
Feel like it might be nice to go out and be admired.
同意 去接受别人的仰慕吧
I agree. Go be admired.
谁知道呢? 也许你还真能培养出感情
Who knows? You may actually simulate human emotion.
- 谢谢  - 谢谢
- Thank you.  - Thank you.
我的脚是内翻的...
My foot actually pronates...
所以我跑起来髂胫束会拉紧 很疼
so my IT band is strained when I run, which is really painful.
足科专家给我做了很棒的矫正器
The foot specialist made me these really great orthotics.
是按照我的脚形做的 现在我跑起来好多了
They shape around my foot. They make it so much better when I'm running.
我完全不能形容这种奇妙的感觉
I cannot explain how amazing it feels.
- 我是那种...  - 天啊 我前夫在这儿
- Actually I'm one of those people who...  - Oh, my God. Oh, my God. My ex is here.
哦 我们还眼神接触了
Oh, we just made eye contact.
- 也许他没看见我  - 我想这... 这没事的
- Maybe he didn't see me.  - I think it's... It's okay.
- 不 他看见我了 他看见我了  - 没事的
- Nope, he saw me. He saw me.  - It's okay.
他过来了 知道吗? 你应该离开这儿
He's coming over here now. Know what? You should leave.
- 什么?  - 没错 你赶快走吧
- What?  - Yeah, you should just go.
- 我不会走的  - 你走了会好点
- I'm not gonna leave.  - It would be better.
太晚了 他已经来了 嘿
It's too late because he's here now. Hey.
- 嘿 最近怎么样?  - 很好啊
- Hey. How's it going?  - Good.
- 觉得应该过来打个招呼 我是杰西  - 这是麦克
- Thought I'd say hi. I'm Jesse.  - That's Mac.
- 我是马克思  - 马特
- It's Max.  - Matt.
- 不是 马克思  - 很好啊
- Nope, Max.  - Nice. Cool.
我们在吃饭 我在约会呢 这是约会哦
We're just eating. I'm on a date. We're on a date. I'm dating.
哦 意大利酱汁是这里的特色
Oh, cool. The puttanesca special is the bomb here.
- 太好了 我就是点的那个  - 很好啊
- Oh, good news. That's what I ordered.  - Nice. Cool.
你跟谁一起来的?
Who are you here with?
我一个人来的 在看湖人的比赛
Oh, I'm just rolling solo, watching the Lakers game.
- 是科比对詹姆斯 对吧?  - 是啊
- It's Kobe-LeBron, right?  - Yes.
- 真让人激动  - 是啊 巅峰对决
- So psyched.  - Yeah, man, epic.
- 我录下来了  - 好啊
- TiVo'd it.  - Nice. Cool.
- 很高兴认识你  - 我也是
- Well, nice to meet you.  - Nice to meet you.
小塞 见到你真好 玩得开心
C, good to see you. Have fun.
他人不错啊
He's cool.
- 谢谢你  - 谢谢你
- Thank you.  - Thank you.
- 你还好吧?  - 什么? 哦 没事啊
- Are you okay?  - What? Oh, nothing.
你喜欢面包吗?
Do you like bread?
真开心 下次还来吗?
That was great. Should we do it again?
星期三? 吃寿司?
Wednesday? Sushi?
- 我想还是算了吧  - 害怕水银中毒?
- I don't think we should.  - Because of the mercury poisoning?
- 我的针灸医生说那只是个谣言  - 不是 我觉得...
- My acupuncturist said that's a myth.  - No. I think that...
我觉得你可以多用点时间来走出离婚的阴影
I think you could use a little more time to get over your divorce.
我也是离婚后很长一段时间才开始约会的 我很理解
I mean, look, it took me a long time to start dating after mine. I get it.
谢谢你的关心 我很好
I appreciate your concern, but I'm fine.
我想我们只是不合适 那么...
I guess you're just not a match for me, so....
是啊 没错...
Yeah. Well...
睡个好觉
have a good night.
- 谢谢  - 祝你好运
- Thanks. Okay.  - And good luck.
随便吧
Whatever.
- 嗨 亲爱的 贝丝  - 嗨 嗨
- Hi, honey. Beth.  - Hi. Hi.
哇哦 你就快喘不上气了 等等 你是跑过来的?
Wow, you're really out of breath. I'm sorry, did you just fucking run here?
- 是啊  - 从你家?
- Yeah.  - From your house?
- 我开始跑步了 真是太有趣了  - 好吧 你都被汗湿透了
- I started running. It's really fun.  - Okay, you're sopping in sweat.
- 好像有12英里?  - 13.6英里
- Isn't that like 12 miles?  - Thirteen-point-six.
跑步很好啊 可以帮我增加脑内啡的释放
But it's good because it just, like, really gets my endorphins up.
让我的脑袋更清醒
It helps me clear my head.
赖利的单子真棘手 我快崩溃了
The Riley account is a handful. I have been so swamped.
很好 看到你这么忙我就放心了 你跟杰西见过面吗?
Good. I'm glad you've been so busy. Have you spoken to Jesse?
碰到过他一次 我觉得他好像胖了
I actually ran into him, and I thought he was actually looking a little fat.
是吗? 我怎么觉得看到他的时候他更健壮了
Really? I feel like when I saw him, he was looking kind of fit.
- 所以你也见过杰西?  - 是啊 是的 我见过他
- So you saw Jesse?  - Yeah. Yeah, I have. I've seen him.
所以你也跟那个叫什么名字的出去了?
And you've hung out with what's-her-name?
维罗妮卡? 是的
Veronica? Yes, I have.
- 可以寄急件吗?  - 她很蠢 是吧?
- Can I get a rush delivery on that?  - She's dumb, right?
不啊 她不蠢 她... 挺简单的
No, she's not dumb. She's... She's simple.
上午7点到晚上9点可以吗?
Does 7 A.M. to 9 P.M. work as a window for you?
简单就是愚蠢嘛
Simple means dumb, though.
真的不是 简单得很优雅
No, actually. Simple in a really elegant way.
优雅
Elegant.
- 那就这样吧  - 是啊 那个时间段很合适
- I think we're done here.  - Yeah, that window is fine.
- 我以为你会为杰西高兴  - 哦 当然了 我很高兴啊
- I thought you would be happy for Jesse.  - Oh, no, I totally am.
我只是看不出来那个莫妮卡哪里优雅了
I just didn't realize that Monica was elegant.
你知道她叫维罗妮卡 说实话 亲爱的 你会喜欢她的
You know her name's Veronica. And honestly, honey, you'd really like her.
拜托 别这样
Okay, don't do that.
你后悔离开杰西了吗?
Are you having regrets about Jesse?
什么? 没有啊 一点都没有
What? No. Not one.
我送你回家吧? 我怕你被汗淹死了
Will you let me drive you home? I'm afraid you'll drown.
好吧 其实我晚上还有个约会 我该洗个澡 对吧?
Okay. I actually have a date tonight. I should probably shower, right?
是啊 没错 该洗个澡
Yeah, I would. Yes, shower.
- 跟谁约会?  - 鲁珀特・贝茨
- Who's the date?  - Rupert Bates.
鲁珀特・贝茨 那个盖普杂志的模特?
Rupert Bates. The Gap model?
天啊 他太性感了 但是他看起来像11岁
Oh, my God. He's so hot. But he's like 11 years old.
其实他22岁了
He's actually 22.
斯基尔斯为我们牵的线 他以后会成为明星的
Skillz set me up with him. He's gonna be a star.
他正在拍"史前两万年" 是"史前一万年"的前传
He's filming 20,000 BC right now, which is the prequel to 10,000 BC.
- 哦 太棒了 我喜欢那部电影  - 我知道
- Oh, fuck, I love that movie.  - I know.
# 一颗星辰划过天幕 #
# A star fell from the sky #
# 看着你 我突然醒悟 #
# Look at you and I realize #
# 这就是你在起舞 #
# It's the way your body moves #
# 依然记得初次谋面 #
# First time that I saw your face #
# 你就像一个小小的天外飞仙 #
# You're like a little alien from outer space #
# 我愿追随到月球 #
# I'm gonna follow you to the moon #
真不错
That was so good.
- 事实上 这是为我妈妈写的  - 你母亲真幸运
- Actually, I wrote it for my mom.  - Lucky lady.
为什么你想跟着她飞到月亮去?
Why do you wanna follow your mom to the moon?
- 她是最棒的 你要见了她 一定会喜欢她的  - 是啊 肯定的
- She's the best. You'd love her if you met her.  - Yeah. I bet.
你怎么认识斯基尔斯的?
So how do you know Skillz?
斯基尔斯给了我一些销魂的小绿叶子
Skillz provides me with the happy smoky green treats.
- 这么好  - 对不起 你实在是...
- Awesome.  - I'm sorry, but you are just...
你好 最特别的唯一
Hello, special one.
不行
No.
这听起来很疯狂 但我完全忘了家里还点着蜡烛
This is crazy, but I just totally forgot I left a candle burning at my house.
- 我得走了  - 好的 快去吧
- I have to go.  - No, of course.
真的很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
等歌写好了我会寄给你一份的
I'll send you a copy of the song when it's done.
我的头发太干了 看起来像一堆草
My hair is so dry. It looks like straw.
- 来点儿阿得拉集中注意力?  - 不要 那玩意儿让我觉得自己像个机器人
- Here, do you want an Adderall?  - No, that shit makes me feel like a robot.
说到机器人 这地方是谁设计的?
Speaking of robot, who the hell designed this place?
感觉就像是星际迷航里面的布景
I feel like Spock is about to walk around the corner.
嗨 赖利 我是塞莱斯特 我是流行论坛的合伙人
Hi, Riley. I'm Celeste. I'm a partner at Pop Forum.
我只是过来做个自我介绍
I just wanted to introduce myself.
你长得还可以
You're kind of pretty.
谢谢 我洗个手
Thank you. I'm just gonna sneak in here.
- 我为什么长红疹了?  - 太多糖 咖啡和酒精
- Why am I breaking out?  - Too much sugar, coffee, alcohol.
我想是我新的护肤"政体"造成的
I think it's my new skin regime. Yeah.
是"养生法"
It's "regimen."
什么?
What?
政体是指政府的管理系统 那个词... 应该是"养生法"
A regime is a system of government. The word is... The word's "regimen."
谢谢 拼字控 很高兴认识你
Thanks, Scrabble. It was really nice to meet you.
考虑到你的品牌认知 我们需要一种你活在当下的感觉
In thinking about your new brand, we wanted a sense of where you currently exist.
为此我们要在全国范围内设立重点行销区域
We set up a number of focus groups throughout the country.
你的民调在中西部地区很高 这很不错
Your testing is really high in the Midwest, which is wonderful.
我们还将会在其他几个城市做调查
We'll be rolling those out to a few different cities.
塞莱斯特已经想了几个关于徽标的点子 都很有创意
Celeste has come up with a number of ideas for logos, which are looking really great.
- 塞莱斯特 你要说吗...?  - 是的 是的
- Celeste, you wanna...?  - Yes. Yes. Here.
我们的第一轮宣传大部分基于...
Our first round is based heavily...
一种嘻哈 复古 带有工业元素的风格
on a kind of hip-hop, retro, throwback, industrial flair.
就是我刚才跟助手萨凡娜说的那个
The one I was talking to my girl Savannah about.
我们希望能迎合城市青少年的口味
Really trying to get the urban flavor in there for the tweens.
你们这儿有什么零食吗?
Do you guys have any snacks?
比如寿司?
Like sushi?
你好啊 最特别的唯一
Hello, special one.
- 听起来好可怕  - 本来就很可怕
- Sounds so awful.  - It was so awful.
那些不靠外表维生的男人都死哪儿去了?
I mean, where are the guys who don't wear makeup for a living?
能不能有点智慧? 智商高点儿又不会死人
How about a little intellect? Intellect never hurt anybody.
- 等等 你没见过尼克 对吧?  - 尼克?
- Wait. You never met Nick, right?  - Nick?
- 尼克・莫兰  - 那个摄影师?
- Nick Moran.  - The photographer?
- 没见过 你认识他?  - 是啊 我们是同学
- No. You know him?  - Yeah, we went to school together.
这将会非常完美
This could be perfect.
约会让我不舒服 我一点都不喜欢约会
I'm uncomfortable with dating, and I don't really like any of it.
相信我 你会喜欢他的
Trust me, you will like him.
也会爱上他的小鸡鸡
And also, I love cock.
你要再努力一点才能成为基佬 斯科特
You gotta work a little harder to integrate the gayness, Scott.
是啊
Yeah.
- 晚安  - 安
- Good night.  - Night.
- 我明天就帮你介绍  - 好
- I'll hook that up tomorrow.  - Great.
接住了 就像这样 贝基
Nailed it. Way to go, Becky.
- 加油 伙计们 对吗?  - 耶!
- Go, team, right?  - Yeah!
- 宝贝背带是什么玩意儿?  - 是一个非常非常袖珍的瑞典男人
- What the fuck is a BabyBjorn?  - It's a very, very tiny Swedish man.
是一种婴儿背带 能让父母跟宝宝更加亲密...
It's actually a child carrier that allows the baby to benefit from intimacy...
而不是只用婴儿车
without the confinement of a stroller.
- 你怎么知道的?  - 贝丝说的
- How do you know that?  - Beth.
没错 我们参加过无数次迎婴派对
Yeah, we go to a lot of baby showers.
而我帮好多女士有了宝宝
I put a lot of babies in the ladies.
- 塞莱斯特最近怎么样?  - 谁?
- How's Celeste?  - Who?
- 塞莱斯特  - 她还行
- Celeste.  - She's all right.
我改良了她对大麻的接受程度 她不错
I'm kind of fine-tuning her cannabis levels right now, but she's okay.
- 她不抽大麻  - 现在抽了 爱不释手
- She doesn't smoke weed.  - She does now. She loves that shit.
史诺普・道格的歌听多了吧
Fucking Snoop Dogg.
婴儿毛巾 抽乳器 尿布? 我去
Birthing towel, breast pump, diaper genie? Fuck.
- 我真的要有个宝宝了  - 你会很棒的
- I'm seriously having a baby.  - You'll do great, man.
嘿 斯基尔斯 你那位朋友是谁?
Hey, Skillz. Who's your buddy?
我不知道 我以为那是你们的朋友
I don't know. I thought he was your friend.
- 不是我的  - 真假?
- Not with me.  - Really?
我不认识他
I don't know him.
我等了估计有21个小时 三个都被我尿湿了
I waited like 21 hours, three of them soaked in my own pee.
- 哦 天呐  - 但是我最终还是拍到卡扎菲了
- Oh, my God.  - But I finally got the shot of Gaddafi.
天呐 我绝对见过这张
My God, I've totally seen this one.
- 你见过了?  - 是啊
- You've seen it?  - Yeah.
- 我超级喜欢 太酷了  - 谢谢
- I'm such a big fan. That's so cool.  - Thank you.
- 我觉得他还在笑  - 没错
- I feel like he's kind of smiling.  - He is.
我觉得是我牛仔裤上那摊尿渍逗他笑的
I mean, I think the piss stain running down my jeans made him laugh.
真的 那天全湿了
Seriously, I was soaked.
全世界都以为你聪明过人 只有我才知道真相是什么
The world will think you're brilliant. I'll be the only one who knows.
怎么了?
What?
- 我在餐厅预订了8点半的座位 现在晚了  - 不是吧
- We missed our reservation for 8:30.  - Oh, no.
你想让我恳求他们 让我们进去吗?
You want me to call down, see if they can still take us?
我该怎么说呢... ?
Should I just, like...?
我们9点或者9点一刻的时候能进去吗?
You guys still take us for like 9, 9:15?
- 我觉得没有人会...  - 行吗?
- I don't think anybody...  - Is that cool?
- 不行吗?  - 是可以
- You can't do that?  - You can.
但我觉得没人会听你的
I just don't think anybody will hear you.
你知道吗? 如果直接叫外卖的话...
You know what? I actually would be cool...
我也没有问题
let's just get room service.
- 外卖?  - 没错
- Room service?  - Yeah.
好啊 叫外卖我没意见
Okay. I could do room service.
- 好吧  - 我喜欢叫外卖
- Cool.  - That sounds good. I like that.
我很高兴能聊的这么开心 认识你很高兴
I'm so happy this worked out. It's so nice to meet you.
我都忘了上次有这种感觉是什么时候了
Can't remember the last time I felt like this.
没错
Yes.
- 你在干吗?  - 你觉得我在干吗?
- What are you doing?  - What do you think I'm doing?
不 不 不 不要这样 刚才还很顺的
No, no, no. Don't do that. Things were going so well.
- 我想让你看着我  - 我不要看你
- I want you to watch me.  - There's no watching.
- 我快了  - 快什么了? 不要 不 我不能...
- I'm almost there.  - Where? Don't. No. I can't...
马上了
Almost there.
哦 来吧 没错
Yeah, come on. That's it.
- 你起来  - 没错 就快了
- Move.  - Yeah, it's coming.
来了 来了
Here it comes. Here it comes.
嘿 希望能见到你
Hey. So I'm glad we can meet up.
我在艾莉希安路上的素食餐厅等你 如果找不到路就联系我
There's this place by me, Vegan Vittles on Elysian Way. Call me if you get lost.
素食餐厅是个什么鬼地方?
What the fuck is a vegan vittle?
就告诉她明天到就行
Just tell her to be here tomorrow.
- 嗨  - 抱歉 稍等一会儿
- Hey.  - Sorry, one second.
发个邮件就好
Just have to send this e-mail.
好了 嗨
There. Hi.
- 嗨 最近好吗?  - 忙死了
- Hi. What's up?  - A lot.
- 能给我来给咖啡吗?  - 我们只有巴拉圭茶
- Can I get some coffee, please?  - We have yerba mate.
- 绿茶呢?  - 我们有无咖啡因绿茶
- Green tea?  - We have decaf green tea.
- 那我就要杯水吧  - 好的 你呢?
- I'll just get some water.  - Okay. Anything for you?
- 我点一份其拉大素餐  - 好的
- I'd like the veganchilada, please.  - Sure.
- 再要一份腰果奶酪沙司  - 好的
- Cashew-cheese sauce on the side.  - Yeah.
我还想看下你们海藻系的菜单
I'd like to take a look at your seaweed menu.
好的 给
Yeah. There you go.
- 不 我不需要 谢谢  - 太好了 要一份波罗的海海带
- No, I'm good, thanks.  - Awesome. Baltic kelp.
- 好的  - 好了就这些 谢谢
- Yep.  - I'll have that. Thank you.
- 你看起来很好啊  - 谢了 你也不差嘛
- You look good.  - Thanks. You look good too.
我一直在猛做普拉提
I've been doing a lot of Pilates.
- 真的?  - 是的 维罗妮卡是个舞者
- Really?  - Yeah. Veronica's a dancer.
所以各种设备都有 我只要用就行了
She has all this equipment at her house, so I've just been getting into it.
呃 我知道整件事情都很怪
Well, I know all this has been really weird.
只有你觉得怪的时候才怪
It's only weird if you think it's weird.
好吧
Okay.
很显然你一直没在离婚协议上签字...
There's apparently a holdup on the divorce papers on your end...
而维罗妮卡不是美国人 所以...
and Veronica's actually not a citizen, so...
- 什么? 她是哪里人?  - 比利时人
- What? Where's she from?  - Belgium.
比利时 优雅
Belgium. Elegant.
- 什么?  - 没什么
- What?  - Nothing.
主要是 我们要结婚了...
Point is, we need to get married...
我很抱歉打扰你 但是确实需要你赶紧签了那些文件
and I'm really sorry to bug you, but I really need you to sign those papers.
好吧 杰西
Okay, Jesse.
我一直忙于工作 因为我们总要有人为生计挣钱...
Well, I've been busy with work, because some of us work for a living...
所以很抱歉我没时间帮你搞好你的新生活
so I'm sorry I haven't had time to focus on helping you get on with your new life.
我知道 我也不愿意总是找你
I know. I'm sorry.
你怎么会认为自己适合当爸爸?
What makes you think you're suitable to be a dad, even?
- 我们从来没聊过要孩子  - 你对孩子的问题总是有所保留
- We never talked about kids.  - You had reservations about kids.
- 我是在和你要孩子上有所保留  - 是 彼此彼此
- I had reservations about kids with you.  - Yeah, well, ditto.
我觉得维罗妮卡会是一个很棒的妈妈
I think Veronica's gonna be an amazing mother.
好极了
Low blow.
我会签了的
I'll sign the papers.
而你很可笑 这个餐厅也很可笑
You're ridiculous. This place is ridiculous.
什么腰果-素食-海带乱七八糟的
Fucking cashew-vegan-kelp bullshit.
杰西居然是素食主义者?
Jesse's a fucking vegan?
没错 一个即将有作品展的素食家
Yeah, a vegan whose work is being shown.
- 在高古轩画廊  - 在高古..?
- At the Gagosian.  - At the Gagos...?
- 什么?  - 没错
- What?  - Yep.
怎么会有人理解他那些作品... ?
How does anybody even know about his art... ?
你知道吗? 我一点都不想知道
You know what? I don't wanna know anything.
天呐 他现在太火了
My God, he's on fire right now.
和我分手是他做过的最正确的事情
Breaking up with me was the best thing he ever did.
- 我也该和自己分手  - 哦 别这样说
- I should break up with me.  - Oh, stop.
别人的成功不等于你的失败啊
Somebody else's success does not mean your demise.
除了杰西
Except for Jesse's.
- 你们今天扮的是谁啊?  - 比伯
- What are you guys dressed as again?  - Bieber.
- 他才剪了村头  - 什么? 我操
- He just got a buzz cut.  - What? Fuck!
- 不是吧  - 什么时候?
- Shut up.  - When?
几个小时前吧 佩雷斯爆料的(美国著名八卦天王)
Like two hours ago. It was on Perez.
- 我去  - 他的头发就是他的全部看点
- Goddamn it.  - His hair was everything.
他才华横溢
He's really talented.
为毛变装派对都要在盛夏举办呢? 不热吗
What's with the costume parties in the middle of the summer? Hot.
我要痛快喝个够
I need to fucking drink.
- 厨房里在玩车炸呢  - 很好
- Car bombs in the fucking kitchen.  - Yes.
- 别  - 好 我去玩 就来
- No.  - Yes, I'm doing that. Yes.
你想等等再去玩吗?
You wanna wait a little bit?
- 我说"车" 你说"炸" 车!  - 炸!
- I say "car," you say "bomb." Car!  - Bomb!
三 二 一 干了!
Three, two, one, drink!
- 三 二 一 她输了  - 行了
- Three, two, one. She lost.  - Come on.
- 她输了  - 对她而言已经不错了...
- She lost.  - That's pretty good for...
不 别装老好人 嘿
No, don't be nice. Hey.
你想要扮成什么?
What even are you supposed to be?
- 是啊  - 什么? 哦 白色垃圾啊
- Yeah.  - What? Oh, white trash.
- 那是什么?  - 就是白色垃圾啊
- What is that?  - White trash.
- 白色"拉稀"? 拉稀?  - 白色垃圾
- White "shrash"? Shrash?  - White trash.
是白色垃圾
It's white trash.
- 塞莱斯特  - 是瑜伽男啊
- Celeste.  - Yoga.
- 我好久没在瑜伽课上见到你了  - 没错 我改成跑步了
- I haven't seen you there in a while.  - I know. I've been running a lot.
- 因为跑步对塑形很有用  - 看出来对你起作用了
- It really helps you keep in better shape.  - I can see that's important to you.
你练得怎么样了?
How's your practice?
很好笑 是白色垃圾吗?
That's funny. White trash?
- 你扮的谁?  - 我很显然是麦片杀手
- What are you?  - I'm a cereal killer, obviously.
嘿 你说的没错
Hey, you were right.
- 什么意思?  - 你说我的事说对了
- What do you mean?  - You were right about me.
关于车 手机...
The car, the phone...
还有瑜伽
the yoga.
除了我读的常春藤学院不对 我上的是康奈尔大学
Except I went to an Ivy League school. I went to Cornell.
- 恭喜你  - 多谢了 老兄
- Congratulations.  - Thanks, man.
- 那就是常春藤了  - 我知道
- That's barely an Ivy.  - I know.
就是了
Barely.
- 你抽烟吗? 在派对上就抽
- Do you smoke?  - At parties.
走吧 我也是
Let's go. Me too.
很抱歉那天在瑜伽馆的事 我每次练完瑜伽都觉得很开放
I'm sorry for that day at the studio. I just feel really open after yoga.
别说"开放" 别这样说
Don't say "open." No.
你的今天的打扮太棒了 你打算毁了它吗
Your costume is so great. You're gonna ruin it.
我开玩笑的 你知道我为什么练瑜伽吗?
I'm kidding. You know why I go to yoga?
我练瑜伽是为了认识女孩
I go to yoga to meet girls.
- 这个我信  - 你信?
- I believe that.  - You do?
嗯
Yeah.
说到这了 咱俩到底什么关系? 我是说 我们之间...?
Speaking of, what's the deal with you and me? I mean, are we...?
是彼此喜欢吗还是有别的问题?
Is it happening or what?
嗯 你和我之间的问题...
Well, the deal with you and me...
是我结婚六年的老公想要离婚...
is that my husband of six years wants a divorce...
因为他想和一个怀了他孩子的女人结婚
because he wants to marry the woman who's carrying his child.
这就是我们之间的问题
That's the deal with you and me.
听起来很难解决啊
Sounds tough.
他几乎不了解她
He barely knows her.
他只是迷失了...
He's just lost...
但他要把所有事都一起搞砸
and he's just going about everything so wrong.
你说的没错
And you're right.
准备怎么办?
Now what?
什么意思?
What does that mean?
我的意思是 你是想要做正确的 还是想要做快乐的?
I mean, do you wanna be right, or do you wanna be happy?
行了 听着 瑜伽男 我不想管对错 因为我就是对的那个 明白?
Okay, listen, Yoga, I don't wanna be right. I know I'm right, okay?
总有人会让你失望 我接受这个事实
People will let you down. I have accepted that fact.
但是既然知道了这些...
But knowing that...
就很难快乐起来
makes it impossible to be happy.
但至少这是真实的
But at least it's fucking real.
从来没人能穿这个垃圾袋还说出处这么一堆...
No one has ever given a more self-righteous monologue...
- 自以为是的独白  - 快闭嘴吧
- wearing a trash bag.  - Shut up.
好了 醉鬼 该回家了
Okay, drunkie, let's go home.
- 我是保罗  - 我是贾斯汀・比伯
- Paul.  - Justin Bieber.
哦贾斯汀・比伯啊 你好
Justin Bieber. Hi.
- 我也是贾斯汀・比伯  - 你好
- Justin Bieber too.  - Hi.
玩笑一下 我是贝丝
Just kidding. Beth.
- 你还想再来一杯吗?  - 多来几杯吧
- You want another drink?  - Two.
- 继续  - 继续
- One drink.  - One drink.
你好 我是杰西 请留言
Hey, you've reached Jesse. Leave me a message.
嗨 我这还有你的一大堆东西 我给你送过去 就这事儿
Hey, I still have a bunch of your shit. I'm just gonna drop it off. Okay.
你会是个很好的爸爸
You're gonna be a really good dad.
怎么会想这么说?
What made you say that?
我也不知道 就是知道你会是
I don't know. I just know it.
对于一个自由艺术家和他的比利时新娘来说真是够奢侈
Well, that's an extravagant purchase for a freelance artist and his Belgian bride.
我靠
Shit.
完了 完了 完了
Shit, shit, shit.
我刚想起来我还不知道你中名呢
I just realized I don't know your middle name.
- 叫古蒂丽芬  - 古蒂丽芙?
- It's Godelieve.  - Goldleaf?
不 是古蒂丽芬 意思是"上帝的关爱"
No, Godelieve. It means "loved by the gods."
是荷兰语
It's Dutch.
- 很好听  - 谢谢
- Pretty.  - Thanks.
- 你的呢?  - 我叫莫迪凯
- What's yours?  - Mordechai.
哦 那是什么意思?
Okay. What does it mean?
意思是我是个绝对的犹太人
It means I'm very, very Jewish.
好吧
Right.
是塞莱斯特吗?
Celeste?
嗨
Hey.
你在这干嘛呢?
Hey. What are you doing here?
我只是把你的东西拿过来
I just was dropping off some of your stuff.
你在垃圾桶里面翻什么呢?
Why were you in the trash can?
我有丢东西
I lost something.
- 丢垃圾桶里面了?  - 是
- In the trash?  - Yeah.
是我的手镯 不过我拿回来了 所以... 没事了
It was my bracelet, but I got it back. So it's... I'm fine.
哦 你记得维罗妮卡吗?
Oh, you remember Veronica.
当然 嗨 哦你已经这么明显了 天呐
Yes. Hi. Wow, you're so pregnant. Oh, my God.
- 是啊  - 我喜欢你的毛衣
- Yeah.  - I love your sweater.
- 哦 谢谢  - 真会赞美
- Oh, thank you.  - Good compliment.
我要走了 我快迟到了 所以...
I'm gonna go, because I'm late for something, so...
你不进去喝杯茶什么的吗?
Sure you don't wanna come in for tea?
不了 不了 你们下午好好休息吧 我要...
No, no, you guys have a good afternight. I'm gonna...
那是我的吗?
Is that mine?
什么? 是 我不知道怎么在我手里...
What? Yeah, I don't know how I got...
- 很高兴见到你们 再见啦  - 好吧
- I'm so glad we did this. Bye, you guys.  - Okay.
从黑暗中走出来迎接光明吧 女孩
Step out of the shadows, girl, and into the light.
一切都会好的 明白吗? 不用担心
Chips are gonna fall, you know? No need to trip.
- 他俩在一起是什么样的?  - 谁俩?
- What are they like together?  - Who?
- 哦 杰西和维罗妮卡?  - 嗯
- Oh, Jesse and Veronica?  - Yeah.
他们很好 你知道吗?
They're okay, you know?
他正努力 但你知道吗? 不是所有美好的东西都在等他
He's trying, but it's not all rainbows and unicorns over there, you know?
- 所以他们不快乐?  - 不 我可没这么说
- So they're not happy?  - No, I didn't say that.
听着 他是我朋友 你知道的...
Listen, he's my friend, you know...
我爱他 但是你也是我的朋友 知道吗?
and I love him, but you're my friend too, you know?
所以只要你需要 像 那种特殊的朋友关系...
And if you ever need, like, any kind of special friendship...
你懂的 就是需要一个异于普通的朋友的人那样...
you know, like, just someone to be with you and hold you...
陪着你抱着你爱抚你对你好的话...
and caress you and be good to you in ways that maybe guys aren't...
我可以做那种朋友
I think I could be that guy.
- 不需要  - 那就好 那就好
- No.  - Good. Good, good.
你住哪儿?
So where do you live?
我住在西木区的一座公寓里
I'm in Westwood, in a condo.
- 不错嘛  - 你会喜欢这里的
- Cool.  - You're gonna love this place.
你活这么大还没这么轻松过吧
Never been so relaxed in your life.
就是这样
There you go.
这绝对是最特别的约会场所
This is a very unique place to take a date.
没错 我一直在这约会
Yeah, I take all my dates here.
- 哦 我还以为我是特别的  - 你的确是
- Oh, I feel so special.  - You are.
对吧 奶奶?
Right, Nana?
她们都是
They all are.
作为一个对的人 你最近过得怎么样?
How's being right going for you?
哦 你知道 不是很顺 真的
Oh, you know, not that well, really.
我正顺风顺水的过着 所以才给你打电话
I was on a real winning streak. That's why I called you.
你知道吗? 我很高兴你联系我
You know what? I'm happy you did.
为什么你要把我带到一个让亚洲人弄的你浑身酸痛的地方?
Why would you take me to a place where Asian people beat you up?
- 那你觉得怎么样?  - 我觉得... 实际上我觉得太赞了
- But how do you feel?  - I feel.... I feel really good, actually.
所以闭嘴吧
So shut up, then.
- 现在我们要干嘛?  - 别试图掌控一切
- What are we doing now?  - Don't try to control everything.
你需要顺其自然 在瑜伽中 也叫做超脱
You need to let go. In yoga, we call it vairagya.
少来瑜伽那套
Don't with the yoga.
- 嗨  - 最近好吗
- Yo.  - What's up.
- 怎么了?  - 最近好吗?
- What's going on?  - How you doing?
- 嘿 这是塞莱斯特  - 塞莱斯特 你好 我是马特
- Hey, this is Celeste.  - Celeste, what's up? Matt.
路易斯在这吗? 在? 人多吗?
Is Louis here? Yeah? Good crowd?
人多吗? 就像你奶奶家一样? 我们在哪?
Good crowd? Like your grandma? Where are we?
这是什么?
What is this?
这是她第一次来这
This is her first time here.
来吧
Check it out.
哦 天呐
Oh, my God.
- 这里太棒了  - 你看起来很吃惊啊
- This place is really cool.  - You sound surprised.
我是吃惊 你可是住西木区的人
I am surprised. You live in Westwood.
- 想喝点什么?  - 啤酒?
- What do you want to drink?  - Beer?
- 好  - 行吗?
- Yeah.  - Yeah?
你好啊 老兄?
How you doing, man?
嗨 宝贝儿 给我来两瓶啤酒
Hi, sweetheart. Can I get two beers?
别烫着自己了 老天
Don't burn yourself. Jesus.
- 谢谢  - 谢谢
- Thank you.  - Thanks.
- 干杯  - 干杯
- Cheers.  - Cheers.
这地方真不错
This is quite a spot.
哦 不
Oh, no.
- 你喜欢跳舞吗?  - 嗯 我猜你也喜欢
- You like to dance?  - Yeah. Guess you do too.
- 你跳的很好  - 哦 你也不赖
- You're good.  - Oh, you're good.
这是什么意思?
What was that for?
超脱的意思 老兄 不去试图掌控一切
Vairagya, bro. Don't try to control everything.
- 我很喜欢那个封面  - 哦 很好 没错我也觉得很漂亮
- I really like the logo.  - Oh, good. Yeah, I think it's perfect.
是啊 波普艺术的影响太广泛了
Yeah, the Keith Haring influence is pretty cool.
是啊 的确是小有影响
Yeah, there is a little bit of that going on.
- 你在嘲笑我吗?  - 没有啊 我只是...
- Are you mocking me?  - No, I just...
你对艺术的了解让我印象深刻
I'm impressed that you know about art.
为什么? 因为我是流行歌手还是因为我是家庭教育长大的?
Why? Because I'm a pop star or because I was homeschooled?
随便你怎么想 但是你知道你的问题在哪吗?
Whatever. Do you know what your problem is?
- 妄下定论  - 你说什么?
- Contempt prior to investigation.  - I'm sorry?
你自以为比别人都聪明 这就是你的黑暗面
You think you're smarter than everybody, and that is your dark little prison.
鞋子很漂亮
Nice shoes.
黑暗面?
Dark little prison?
你不了解我的人生 不知道我是谁
You don't know my life. You don't know me.
你懂什么叫黑暗面 黑暗面就是只靠穿着露脐装维持生计
You know what's a dark little prison is having to wear midriffs for a living.
那才是黑暗面 省省吧
That's a dark little prison. Give me a break.
这才是我要说的
That's what I'm talking about.
我操啊
What the fuck?
- 我又开始抽烟了  - 看出来了
- I started smoking again.  - Yeah, I can see that.
我不知道你有哪些底线 但我敢肯定我在打破它们...
I don't know what the rules are, and I'm sure I'm breaking them...
但是我真的想你了
but I really miss you.
你想进来吗?
Do you wanna come in?
维罗妮卡和画廊里的助理是好朋友
Veronica's actually pretty good friends with the assistant gallerist there...
他很喜欢我的作品 所以...
and he really liked my stuff, so....
- 我也不知道 走着瞧吧  - 杰西 这很好啊
- I don't know, we'll see.  - Jess, that's so great.
- 我很替你开心啊 -是啊
- I'm so happy for you.  - Yeah.
是啊 太棒了
Yeah, it's great.
- 我应该回家了  - 是啊
- I should probably get home.  - Yeah.
很高兴见到你
It's really nice to see you.
你该走了
You should go.
我们能在这稍微躺一会儿吗?
Can't we just lie here a little bit?
真不敢相信我有了孩子 却不是和你的
Can't believe I'm having a baby and it's not with you.
喂?
Yeah?
嘿 我们出了个大问题
Hey, we have a massive problem on our hands.
我不... 我不明白什么意思
I don't... I don't see anything.
这是爆菊啊
It's a penis and a butt.
什么? 不是吧 我没... 我看不出来啊
Really? No, I don't... I don't see it.
这是根阴茎 而这是这个阴茎插进屁股里
There's a penis, and there's the penis going into the butt.
哦 天呐
Oh, my God.
哦 我的天呐 这是个鸡鸡... 这是个鸡鸡... 这是个爆菊
Oh, my God, it's a cock... It's a cock... It's a cock in a butt.
哦 我的天...
Oh, my Go...
哦 天呐 太糟糕了
Oh, my God. That's really bad.
这不是玩笑 塞莱斯特
This isn't a joke, Celeste.
封面上有性行为的标志
There's homosexual butt sex in the logo.
赖利以为我们傻吗? 我想说 这都是群什么烂货啊?
Does Riley think we're stupid? I mean, who are these sick people?
我们目前还没法联系到赖利本人...
Neither Riley nor a representative from Pop Form...
以及流行论坛设计公司的发言人联系上...
the marketing company responsible, could be reached...
给你
There you go.
- 如果需要别的就给我说一声  - 谢谢
- Let me know if you need anything else.  - Thanks.
- 嗨  - 嗨
- Hey.  - Hey.
谢谢你能出来见我
Thanks for meeting me here.
我也不知道该穿什么出来
I don't know what I'm wearing.
- 你看起来像个养猫的疯女人  - 是啊
- You kind of look like a crazy cat lady.  - Yeah.
我不能买漂亮的衣服 因为我会糟蹋了的 你懂吗?
I just can't buy anything nice, because they'll just ruin it, you know?
- 听我说 塞莱斯特...  - 让我先说 好吗?
- Look, Celeste...  - No, let me just say something, okay?
我不知道你那边情况怎么样...
I don't know what's going on in your other situation...
不过我只是想说 我搞砸了
but for the record, I fucked up.
过去我对你很漫不经心 还认为理所应当
I was cavalier with you, and I took us for granted.
我知道这很疯狂 但是若不这样我会觉得被怠慢...
And I know this sounds crazy, but I would be remiss if I didn't just...
如果你能接受 我一定能...
If you were open to it, I feel like I could do better...
更好的处理我们的关系
with you, with us.
我想知道我们还有没有希望
And if there is still a chance, I'd love to know.
杰西啊
Jesse.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我不能这么做
I can't.
嘿
Hey.
嘿 你昨晚为什么过来?
Hey. Why'd you come over last night?
- 我不知道  - 不 我想你很清楚
- I don't know.  - No, I think you do know.
- 那就是个错误 我不该去  - 你个懦夫
- It was a mistake. I shouldn't have come.  - You fucking coward.
我和别人有孩子了
I'm having a baby.
我必须和维罗妮卡好好过日子
I need to figure out a way to make it work with Veronica.
- 我正在尝试改变  - 你为什么不肯为我改变?
- I'm trying to change.  - Why didn't you change for me?
我觉得你根本不需要我改变
I don't think you really wanted me to.
哇哦 我一直在等你成熟起来
Wow. Wow. All I did was wait for you to grow up.
我一直支持你 我为一切买单
I rooted for you. I fucking paid for everything.
- 我为你付出一切  - 是啊 但是我永远赶不上你
- I did everything for you.  - Yeah, and I was never your equal.
我觉得你喜欢这样的生活
And you know what,I think you preferred it that way.
等等 我知道我的成就让你不安
Wait. Wait. I know that my success was never okay for you.
- 你到底想怎样?  - 我要你承认错误
- What do you want?  - I want you to admit that you're wrong.
我做错了什么?
Wrong about what?
你到底想要我怎么做 等你先和别人约会?
What did you expect me to do, wait for you to meet someone first?
这就是你想要的?
Is that how you saw it happening?
听着 我也不想这么快就约会 但是已经发生了
Look, I didn't expect to meet someone so fast, but I did.
我有机会抓住幸福 我不想搞砸
I have a real chance of being happy. I don't wanna blow that.
你知道什么 杰西? 你一定会搞砸
Well, you know what, Jesse? You definitely will blow it.
我真为你悲哀
You know, I feel sorry for you.
你或许会孤独终老
You might actually be alone your whole life.
- 永远别给我打电话  - 放心 我不会的
- Don't ever call me.  - Yeah, don't worry about it.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
别这样
No, no.
好吧
Okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 他好悲伤  - 没错
- He's so sad.  - Totally.
等一下
Wait.
不对 他在画兔子 他很高兴
No. He's painting little rabbits. He's so happy.
我能看出来 他很悲伤 我去过艺术展
He's so sad. I know. I went to art camp.
什么?
Oh, word?
靠
Fuck.
好吧
All right.
要堕落就现在堕落吧
If that's how it's going down, that's how it's going down right now.
抽吧
Hit it. Go get it.
这是近几个月来最开心的事情了
That's the best thing that's happened to me in months.
会时来运转的
Shit will get better.
会吗? 你都不了解
Will it? You don't know that.
- 真没想到他会这样对我  - 谁? 杰西吗?
- I can't believe he did this to me.  - Who? J?
他没做错什么 是你想要离婚的
He didn't do nothing. You wanted a divorce.
没错 但是我不想以这种方式收场
Yeah, but I didn't want it like this.
如果改变不了环境
When we're no longer able to change a situation...
那就改变自己吧
we're challenged to change ourselves.
维克多・弗兰克(心理学家)说的
Viktor Frankl.
也可能是大大小小(说唱歌手)说的
Or Biggie Smalls. It might be Biggie Smalls.
我不记得了
I don't know. I don't remember.
靠 我嗑高了 你高了吗?
Fuck, man. I am fucking high. Are you high?
我嗨爆了 得走了
I'm so high. All right, I gotta go.
- 我能跟你去吗?  - 不行
- Can I come?  - No.
- 能给我带点玉米卷吗?  - 不能
- Can you get me some Del Taco?  - No.
你觉得奥巴马夫妇是真心相爱吗?
Do you think the Obamas really love each other?
是的 我相信
Yeah. Yeah, I really do.
没问题了吧
No more questions.
嗑药小心点 那对孩子不益
Take it easy on that shit. It is not for kids.
嗨
Hey.
- 嗨 亲爱的  - 嗨
- Hi, honey.  - Hi.
- 还记得艾琳吧  - 还有沙拉酱吗?
- You remember Eileen.  - You have more ranch dressing?
- 太好吃了  - 你吃完...?
- It's the fucking bomb.  - Did you finish...?
贝丝就要结婚了
Beth is getting married.
我也曾结过婚 还记得吗? 你们以后一定会有矛盾的
I was married once. You remember? These guys are in for a fucking dogfight.
- 我给你倒杯苏打水吧  - 有矛盾
- Let's go get you a soda.  - A dogfight.
矛盾重重
You're a dogfight.
我不想孤独终老
I don't wanna be alone forever.
亲爱的 你不会孤独终老的
Oh, honey. You're not gonna be alone forever.
你只是需要点时间重振旗鼓
You're just in a time-out till you sober up.
我就坐这里 不会再让你尴尬了 好吧?
I'm gonna sit here. I'm not gonna embarrass you, okay?
- 好的  - 好的
- Okay.  - Okay.
我们应该让尼克・诺尔蒂离开 是吧?
We should get Nick Nolte out of here, huh?
嘿 赖利 我想跟你谈一下...
Hey, Riley. I am calling to talk to you...
封面上的错误
about the error in your logo.
我真的非常非常抱歉
I'm so, so sorry.
我想告诉你我正在尽力补救
And I just wanna let you know that I am on top of it.
请回话 谢谢
Please call me back. Thank you.
你觉得我应该穿这件碎花的还是玫瑰花的?
Do you feel like the dress I'm wearing reads more like eggshell or rose petal?
玫瑰花瓣不错 连着两天都穿碎花太单调了
Rose petal's okay. Eggshell is too whitish to do two days in a row.
- 你看起来棒极了  - 亲爱的 我需要你的帮助
- You look great.  - Honey, I need your help.
我还有一小时 你欠我的哦...
I have like an hour, and you owe me...
因为你昨天让我难堪
because you humped my nana yesterday.
赖利・班克斯知道什么啊?
The fuck does Riley Banks know?
什么都不知道 她就是个烂人
Nothing. She's a tart.
没错 她是烂人 也就有性感的身材罢了
Yes, she's a tart. She's got a cute little hot bod.
- 她资质平平  - 没到平均值
- She's moderately talented.  - Not even.
- 五年后她就会一脸皱纹  - 可能三年或四年就会的
- Five years and it's a wrap on that face.  - If. Three, four.
她为何戳中我的痛处?
Why is she telling me anything about my life?
她就是个愚蠢的小...
She's a stupid litt...
- 天啊 我的天啊  - 怎么了?
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God.  - What?
我还没挂断电话 一直在录音
I never hung up. I didn't hang up the call.
完蛋了
Crap.
接电话吧
You gotta get it.
嗨 赖利 有事儿吗?
Hey, Riley, what's up?
嗨
Hi.
听我说 我... 这里真漂亮
Listen, I... This is a really nice place.
事实上 最近我的日子很不好过
The thing is, I've been having a hard time in my own life.
因此当你说我藐视别人的时候...
So when you said that thing about contempt and investigation...
你就不能闭嘴吗?
Can you just shut up for a minute?
我刚刚发现男朋友背叛了我
I just found out that my boyfriend cheated on me.
哦 天啊 抱歉 我都不知道你有男朋友
Oh. Oh, God, I'm so sorry. I didn't even know you had a boyfriend.
是啊 没人知道
Yeah, exactly. Nobody knew.
他不想别人知道 怕影响他的形象...
He didn't want anyone to know, because it would be bad for his image and....
真是个混蛋
He's just such a fucking asshole.
现在我的前途也要毁了 就因为你在我的封面上放了个阴茎
Now my career might be over because you decided to put a penis in my logo.
- 真得"谢谢"你啊  - 真的很抱歉 非常抱歉
- Thank you for that.  - I know. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
过来
Come here.
- 干嘛?  - 到这来 没事的
- Why?  - Come here. Just come here. It's okay.
没事的 没事了
It's okay. It's okay.
我现在身心俱疲
I'm just so sad. And tired.
我要和你一样孤苦伶仃了
And now I'm gonna be alone like you.
你现在语无伦次 会没事的
Okay, you don't know what you're saying right now. It's okay.
你看体育节目竟然会哭?
Are you crying about sports?
这让我想到了一些往事
Just reminds me of someone.
跟那个女孩有关吗?
Is this about a girl?
- 我不是同性恋  - 知道 我是指那个男的
- I'm not gay.  - No, I know. I meant a boy.
没错
Yeah.
你想他吗?
Do you miss him?
嗯 想他
Yeah, I do.
他们都是混蛋
They all fucking suck.
没错
Kind of.
真的不会好起来吗? 就算你年华已逝?
It really never gets better? Like, not even when you're old?
是啊
No.
不过你可以
But you do.
- 能再抱抱吗?  - 好吧
- Can we hug again?  - Yeah.
不会的 靠
I won't, no. Crap.
不会的 我到机场了
No, no, no. I'm at the airport.
贝丝 我就坐在候机厅
Beth, I'm sitting at the gate.
我当然穿礼服了
Of course I have my dress.
嗨 先生 抱歉打扰你 能让我插个队吗?
Hi, sir. I'm so sorry to bother you, but is there any way I could cut in line?
我要赶去当伴娘 嗨 抱歉打扰你
I'm the maid of honor at this wedding. Hi. I'm sorry to bother you.
你可能听到我刚才和最后那位男士的对话了 我真的着急取回礼服
Maybe you heard me talking to the last gentleman, but I need to get my dress.
当时她正和西班牙人热恋
She pursued her love of Spanish man
但却对她的塔克异常想念
but missed her Tucker more than just a friend.
后来我们的公主与她挚爱的王子一同归家
Our princess returned home to her loving prince
从此他们过上了幸福的生活
and they've been together ever since.
我们爱你 贝丝
We love you, Bethy.
现在该塞莱斯特发言了...
Now we're gonna turn it over to Celeste...
她是贝丝最好的朋友
Beth's best friend in the world.
哇哦 这个... 谢谢了 美女们
Wow. That... Thanks, girls.
真的... 真的不知道说什么好
That was.... There are no words for what that was.
呃... 怎样让修女怀孕? 和她做爱
Um... Ahem. How do you get a nun pregnant? You fuck her.
谢谢你捧场 牧师 感激不尽
Thank you, Reverend. Appreciate it a lot.
从洛杉矶到罗德岛真不容易
It is not easy to get to Rhode Island from Los Angeles.
先要做出租到机场 再做出租到火车站 还要到租车厂
There was a cab to a plane to a cab to a train to a rental car.
可能还要做人力车
There was maybe a rickshaw in there somewhere.
甚至可能要骑驴
Somewhere a donkey.
但是事实上...
But the truth is...
我愿意为贝丝到任何地方...
I would go anywhere for Beth...
因为她是我最好的朋友 我非常爱她...
because she's my best friend and I love her so much...
我真为她高兴
and I'm so happy for her.
在大学快毕业那年 我们有个传统
When we were in college, senior year we had this tradition.
贝丝和塔克还有我和杰西...
Beth and Tucker and me and Jesse would meet...
每周日都去拜访主教 无论是晴天还是阴天
come rain or shine, every Sunday at the Bishop.
他们两个总是有些暧昧...
And there was always something there with these two...
尽管当时他们还是朋友
even though they were just friends.
他们很有默契
Just, like, an ease that they had with each other.
他们是天作之合
They are perfect.
最后 爱情战胜了一切
At last, love wins.
贝丝和塔克...
Beth and Tucker...
你们很幸运 如此幸运能成为好朋友
you guys are lucky, so lucky to be best friends.
你们要懂得珍惜
Work hard at that.
还要懂得感恩
And respect that.
要有耐心
Be patient.
还有...
And...
不必事事较真
you don't always have to be right.
即使你是对的...
Even if you are...
也不要太计较
doesn't fucking matter anyway.
要为爱奋斗每一天
Fight for it every day.
真希望我当时能懂
I wish I had.
祝贺你们
Cheers.
可能现在说这个不合时宜...
This might not be the best time to talk about it...
不过我们也许该赞一下塔克的舞步
but at some point we're gonna have to address Tucker's dance moves.
他真的很特别
He's so special.
你的发言...
So your speech was...
不错啊
beautiful
谢谢
Thank you.
我是发自肺腑的
I meant it.
我知道
I know.
你知道还有什么不错吗?
You know what else is beautiful?
- 哦 不是吧  - 哦 是的
- Oh, no.  - Oh, yes.
- 这个可以吗?  - 可以
- Do we dare?  - We do.
- 在大家眼皮底下?  - 没错
- Here, in front of everyone?  - Of course.
- 好吧 就一次  - 哦 天啊
- All right, maybe just once.  - Oh, my God.
- 跟我说话啊 哦  - 哦 天啊
- Talk to me. Oh, yeah.  - Oh, God.
尖尖头 粗粗茎
Pointy tip, thick stem.
- 坏男孩  - 在长大了
- You're a bad boy.  - You're a grower.
你早都毕业了 变得成熟了
You have graduated and moved on to an adult life.
- 天啊 不要  - 哦 不要
- Oh, God. Oh, no.  - Oh, God. Oh, no.
- 我不是个大根的玉米笋  - 哦 天哪
- I'm a baby corn. I'm not a big corn.  - Oh, my God.
- 哦 天啊  - 天啊
- Oh, my God.  - Oh, God.
老兄 这太邪恶了
Oh, dude, it's so rotten.
嗨
Hey.
- 嗨  - 你们干什么呢?
- Hey.  - What are you guys doing?
- 哦 没什么 就是...  - 是杰西和我经常玩的游戏
- Oh, nothing. Just....  - It's this thing that Jesse and I do.
我们把这个东西当做 一个小阴茎...
We take this thing that resembles, like, a tiny little penis...
然后我们 就像...
and then we, like...
- 我不太懂  - 不过是个蠢游戏
- I don't really get it.  - It's stupid.
- 是挺蠢的  - 晚宴就要开始了
- It's stupid.  - They're about to serve dinner.
- 好的  - 去坐下吧?
- Okay.  - Wanna sit down?
好的
Yeah, yeah.
- 舞池见 怎么样 塞莱斯特?  - 好的
- See you on the dance floor, Celeste?  - Yeah.
来啊 做一个嘛
Do it, do it, do it.
- 我爱你 亲爱的  - 我爱你 亲爱的
- I love you, baby.  - I love you, baby.
你的发言逊毙了
It sounds like the most embarrassing speech ever.
你以后怎么还有脸出现在你朋友面前?
How are you gonna show your face in front of your friends again?
是啊 很奇怪 我挺高兴那么做 不管怎样我觉得好些了
Yeah, well, weirdly, I'm happy that I did it. I feel better somehow.
这首歌是我的最爱! 耶!
This song is my bitch! Yeah!
- 基佬还挺会搞派对的 不是吗?  - 你什么意思?
- The gays really know how to party, huh?  - What do you mean?
这是同志俱乐部
This is a gay club.
这只是首场 以后会发展成什么样说不准呢
It's opening night. It doesn't know what it is yet.
- 赖利 这里被称作"吞吐"  - 我还和那家伙约过会
- Riley, the club is called Swallow.  - I totally dated that guy.
打扰一下 你能转告赖利 我们很崇拜她吗?
Excuse me. Could you tell your friend Riley that we worship her?
她太美了
She's so pretty.
没问题 等她跳完舞我就告诉他
Sure. I'll tell her when she's done dancing.
- 你没发现那个标志是个...?  - 爆菊标志吗? 注意到了
- You are aware that the logo is a...?  - A dick in a butt? Yeah.
我的朋友都很喜欢这个 它就像是同志穿的服装
All of our friends are, like, rocking it. It's kind of become like gay Izod.
太赞了
It's amazing.
- 嗨  - 虽然年轻人不喜欢她了...
- Yo.  - The tweens don't want her anymore...
斯科特 但是同志们喜欢
Scott, but the gays do.
你也是同志 站在同志的角度上思考 美国有十分之一的人是同性恋
You're gay. Start thinking gay. Ten percent of Americans are gay.
同志的最爱 太棒了
Gay Izod. It's great.
明年此时她就能像Lady Gaga一样火了 市场潜力无限啊
She could be Lady Gaga by this time next year. Huge market.
或许你能让爆菊标志发扬光大呢
You might have turned the cock in the butt around.
这个将会一发不可收拾
Cock in the butt is gonna be huge.
嗨
Hi.
我得38分 加上你欠我的50分
Thirty-eight points for me, plus 50 points for using all my tiles.
- 等一下 起名"祖伊莎"怎么样?  - 是啊
- Wait, wait, wait. "Zooecia"?  - Yeah.
不 那不是个单词 是我堂弟的名字
No, that's not a word. That's my hoochie cousin's name.
有一晚我到这泡吧 有个怪人和我穿的一样
So I was at this club the other night, and there was a tranny dressed like me.
- 天啊 真不错  - 我知道
- Oh, my God, that's so sweet.  - I know.
- 他是你的粉丝  - 而且他很性感
- That's a huge compliment.  - He was so hot too.
- 我还是我  - 真不错
- I mean, it was still me.  - That is so sweet.
- 嗨 塞莱斯特  - 嗨 鲁珀特
- Celeste.  - Rupert.
你都没给我打过电话
You never called me back.
你了解的 我弄丢了...
You know, I think I lost my....
- 你认识赖利吗? 这位是鲁珀特  - 嗨 其实我是他的超级粉丝
- Do you know Riley? This is Rupert.  - Hi. I'm actually a big fan.
我也是你的超级粉丝
Likewise.
从这开始 这里开唱
Get in there. Get in there.
好温柔
Very gentle.
这里帮我唱一下
Help me out here.
好了 该一起唱了
All right, both of us.
不行
I can't do it.
很抱歉
This. I'm sorry.
什么意思? 你是认真的吗? 为什么?
What do you mean? Are you serious? Why?
我...
I...
我想保持单身
I think I need to be alone.
- 我正准备离婚  - 我知道你要离婚
- I'm getting a divorce.  - I know you're getting divorced.
我觉得应该一个人处理这件事
I know, but I think I have to do that alone.
好吧
Yeah.
我尊重你的选择
I respect that.
你准备好了再去做 别强迫自己
You're not ready till you're ready. Don't force it.
我指的是瑜伽
That's some yoga shit.
不过我喜欢你
But I like you.
当你准备好了 打电话给我
So when you're ready, if you're ready, you call me.
好吗?
Okay?
在这里和这里签名
And sign here and here.
- 这里吗?  - 是的
- There?  - Yeah.
这里首字母要大写
And initial here, sign here.
还有...
And...
- 这里 这里 都要签  - 领带不错
- Here, sign, and here.  - I like that tie.
哦 谢谢
Oh, thanks.
是有机纤维的吗?
Is it made out of organic mung beans?
不 实际上 我从你丢掉的垃圾里翻出来的
No, actually, I found it digging through your trash.
好吧 我们离婚了
Well, we're divorced.
没错
Yep.
我们做得到了
We did it.
我们成功离婚了
We nailed that divorce.
你准备做什么?
What are you doing right now?
粤语口音 完全听不懂他们在说什么
Cantonese voices. No respect for when their mouths are actually open.
天啊 我觉得我做不到
Oh, my God. I don't think I could focus on it.
你不行 那一点都不性感 不过很有趣
You couldn't. It's not sexy, but it's damn funny.
真漂亮
It's beautiful.
我以为你不喜欢呢
I thought you hated it.
从来没在晚上看见过
Never seen it at night.
嗨
Hey.
虽然我们离婚了 但也不是死人了 是吧?
I know we just got divorced, but nobody died, right?
我也不知道怎么了 就是...
I don't know. It's just....
我在想要怎么样...
I was just thinking about how...
你说的没错
you were right.
我都不知道自己在做什么
I don't know what I'm doing.
你爱她吗?
Do you love her?
那么奋斗也是值得的
Then it's worth fighting for.
好吧
Okay.
我知道你为什么老是哭哭唧唧的了
Now I know why you fucking cry all the time.
- 是在宣泄情感  - 我一直都想告诉你
- This shit's emotional.  - I've been trying to tell you.
你应该幸福
You deserve to be happy.
我一直希望你能幸福
And I want that for you. Always.
我也是
Me too.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you too.
- 很晚了 我送你去停车场  - 是应该这样
- It's late. I'm gonna walk you to your car.  - You probably should.
没错 我可不希望你被某个交响乐团的人抢劫
I should. I don't want you to get mugged by someone from the philharmonic.
没错
Good idea.
嗨 我是保罗 请留言
Hey, you've reached Paul. Leave a message.
嗨
Hey.
可能你正在把名片给瑜伽馆的某个女孩...
You're probably giving your card to some girl in yoga right now...
不过要是还没找到合适的...
but if that doesn't work out for you...
我已经准备好...
I think I'm ready...
跟你对决拼字游戏了
to beat you in Scrabble.
好了 就这些
Okay.
嗨
Hi.
- 打扰一下 先生?  - 有事儿吗?
- Excuse me, sir?  - Yeah?
没事
Never mind.
抱歉我插队了
I'm so sorry for cutting.
我的狗狗在车里 他渴得不行 谢谢了
My dog's in the car and he's really thirsty, so thanks.
没关系
No problem.
嗨
Hi.
-=圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/=-
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 景鲤
翻译: 夏夏潇潇潇 苏菲仙五填坑中 兜兜 水果哥
校对: 影子 veray